Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Music Scores:
  - "There's A Great Day Coming Manana", from "Hold On To Your Hats", words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Burton Lang, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1960 (Box 60)
  - "There's Joy In My Heart", by Mana-Zucca, lyrics by Irwin M. Cassell, Congress Music Publications, Miami, Florida, 5 pages, 1945 (Box 60)
  - "There's A Small Hotel", from the musical comedy, "On Your Toes", music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, Chappell and Co., Inc., 5 pages, 1936 (Box 60)
  - "There Is Nothing Like A Dame", music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, Williamson Music Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "There Must Be Somethin' Better Than Love", from "Arms and the Girl!", lyrics by Dorothy Fields and music by Morton Gould, Chappell and Co., Ltd., New York, 7 pages, 1950 (Box 60)
  - "They Didn't Believe Me", words by Herbert Reynolds, music by Jerome Kern, T. B. Harms Co., New York, 5 pages, 1914 (Box 60)
  - "They Met In Rio (A Midnight Serenade)", lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Harry Warren, Miller Music, Inc., New York, 4 pages, 1941 (Box 60)
  - "They That Sow In Tears", sacred song, by James H. Rogers, G. Schirmer, New York, 6 pages, 1908 (Box 60)
  - "They That Trust In The Lord", sacred song, by John Prindle Scott, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1921 (Box 60)
  - "Thine Alone", from "Eileen", lyrics by Henry Blossom, music by Victor Herbert, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1929 (Box 60)
  - "Think On Me", words and music by Lady John Scott, Patterson's Publications, Ltd., London, 3 pages, 1931 (Box 60)
  - "37 Songs and Scenas by Mozart", edited by J. Pittman and Myles D. Foster, Boosey and Co., Ltd., London, England, 228 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "This Can't Be Love", from "The Boys From Syracuse", lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, book and direction by George Abbott, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "This Is The First", words and music by Wally Peterson, from Lawrence Wright's "On With The Show", Mills Music Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "This Nearly Was Mine", from "South Pacific", music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, Williamson Music Inc., 7 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "This Night (Will Be My Souvenir)", words by Gus Kahn, music by Harry Warren, Bregman, Vocco and Conn., Inc., New York, 3 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "3 Cantos Populares Hespanhoes, Salta Nina En Mi Barquelle", Francisco Mignone, E. L. Mangione, Las Paules, 7 pages, Spanish translation, 1941 (Box 60)
  - "3 Cantos Populares Hspanhoes, Si Quieras Que Yo Te Quiera", Francisco Mignone, E. L. Mangione, Las Paules, 5 pages, Spanish translation, undated (Box 60)
  - "Three English Songs: Sweet Music", Karol Rathaus, Associated Music Publishers, Inc., New York, 6 pages, authographed, 1946 (Box 60)
  - "Three Little Fairy Songs", words by J.L. Crommelin Brown, music by Maurice Besly, Chappell and Co., Ltd., New York, 7 pages, 1912 (Box 60)
  - "Three Sacred Songs", F. Flaxington Harker, G. Schirmer, New York, 7 pages, 1910 (Box 60)
  - "Through A Long and Sleepless Night", from "Come To The Stable", Miller Music Corporation, New York, 3 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "Till The Clouds Roll By", words by Jerome Kern, P. G. Wodehouse and Bolton, music by Jerome Kern, T. B. Harms Company, New York, 5 pages, 1917 (Box 60)
  - "Time On My Hands" (You In My Arms), words by Harols Adamson and Mack Gordon, music by Vincent Youmans, 5 pages, 1930 (Box 60)
  - "Time Was (Duerme)", English lyrics by S,K, Russell, music by Migues Prado, Spanish lyrics by Gabriel Luna, Southern Music Publishing Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1929, 1931 (Box 60)
  - "Time", "You Old Gipsey", The poem by Ralph Hodgson, music by Maurice Besly, Bookey and Company, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1924 (Box 60)
  - "Tipple's Love Song", words and music by Helen Thomas, The Boston Music Co., Boston, Mass., 5 pages, 1947 (Box 60)
  - "To Be In Love", "A Fantastical Love Song", Howard, Wintgreen Music Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1957 (Box 60)
  - "To Dance, To Dream", "Tales From The Vienna Woods", vocal adaptation and lyrics by Ann Ronell, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 11 pages, 1951 (Box 60)
  - "Today I Heard The Grass Grow", words y Laurel Wallace, music by Charles Heurter, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1950 (Box 60)
  - "Together", by B. G. DeSylva, Lew Brown, Ray Henderson, DeSylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1928 (Box 60)
  - "Tomorrow Sings", words by S.A. DeWitt, music by Jacques Wolfe, Carl Fischer, Inc., New York, 11 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "Tonight We Love", words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, Famous Music Corp., New York, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "Too Good For The Average Man", from the musical comedy "On Your Toes", music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, Chappell and Co., Inc., N.Y.C, 5 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "To One Who Passed Whistling Through The Night", Margery Agrell, C. Armstrong Gibbs, Curwen Edition, 7 pages, 1921 (Box 60)
  - "To The Queen of Heaven", by Thomas F. Dunhill, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1926 (Box 60)
  - "Tovarich!", Mana-Zucca, lyrics by Ben M. Kaye, Congress Music Publications, Miami, Florida, 5 pages, 1943 (Box 60)
  - "To You Eternally", words by Christopher Hassall, music by Stanford Robinson, Boosey and Hawkes, 8 pages, 1946 (Box 60)
  - "To You", words and music by Benny Davis, Tommy Dorsey, and Ted Shapiro, Paramount Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Traditional Songs of France", freely arranged by Arnold Bax, Murdock, Murdock and Co., London and Branches, England, 30 pages, 1921 (Box 60)
  - "The Trees and The Master", sacred songs, poem by Sidney Lanier, music by Daniel Protheroe, The Boston Music Company, Boston Mass., 5 pages, 1927 (Box 60)
  - "Trot Here and There", from "Veronique", words by Lillian Eldee and Percy Greenbank, music by Messager, Chappell and Co., Ltd., 3 pages, 1904 (Box 60)
  - "Trouble Is A Man", words and music by Alec Wilder, Recent Music Corporation, New York, 3 pages, 1944 (Box 60)
  - "True Love", music and lyrics by Cole Porter, from "High Society", Buxton Hill Music Corporation, 5 pages, 1955, 1956 (Box 60)
  - "Tuas Maos", Versos de Colobina, musica de Francisco Mignone, Carlos Wehrs and Cia., Ltd., 4 pages, 1936 (Box 60)
  - "Tu-li-Tulip-Time", words by Jack Lawrence, music by Maria Grever, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "Two Offeratory Solos: To-day If We Will", by James H. Rogers and "Hear His Voice", by Francies J. Sadler, The Arthur P. Schmidt Co., Boston and New York, 5 pages, 1904 (Box 60)
  - "Two-Part Choruses", Wood Octavo Series, The B.F. Wood Music Co., Boston, Mass, 6 pages, 1931 (Box 60)
  - "Two Songs: My Mother's Eyes", by R. Huntington, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1926 (Box 60)
  - "The Virgin's Slumber Song", Max Reger, Boston: Oliver Ditson Company, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1912 (Box 60)
  - "Vocal Gems", in "Knickerbocker Holiday", Crowford Music Corporation, New York, 38 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "The Voice In The Wilderness", John Prindle Scott, from the text of Isaiah XL 3.6.7.8., 7 pages, 1916 (Box 60)
  - "Why Can't You Behave", in "Kiss Me Kate", music and lyrics by Cole Porter, book by Sam and Bella Spewack, T. B. Harms Company, Buxton Hill Music Corporation, 5 pages, 1948 (Box 60)
  - "Wishing (Will Make It So)", words and music by B.G. DeSylva, R.K.O. Radio Pictures, Inc., presents "Love Affair", Crawford Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "The Whistling Rabbit", words and music by Mann Curtis, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1953 (Box 60)
  - "Would You Like To Take A Walk (Sump'n Good'll Come From That)", lyrics by Mort Dixon and Billy Rose, music by Harry Warren, Remick Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1930 (Box 60)
  - "Yesterdays", lyrics by Otto Harbach, music by Jerome Kern, T. B. Harms, New York, 5 pages, 1933 (Box 60)
  - "You're The Cream In My Coffee", from "Hold Everything", words and music by B. G. DeSylva, Lew Brown, Ray Henderson, Crawford Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1928 (Box 60)
  - "Your Big Song Folio", Mills Music, Inc., New York, 88 pages, 1954 (Box 60)
- Music Scores, Loose-Leaf:
  - "Hello, Young Lovers", words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 7 pages, 1951 (Box 60)
  - "I Can Dream, Can't I?", words by Irving Kahal, music by Sammy Fain, Chappell and Co., Inc., N.Y.C., 5 pages, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "I Didn't Know What Time It Was", words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - Lyrics by Jack Lawrence, music by Walter Gross, 2 pages, 1947 (Box 60)
  - "Mia Speranza Adorata!", W. A. Mozart, 1 page, undated (Box 60)
  - "Sail! Sail! Sail!", Post Music Co., Inc., 2 pages, 1950 (Box 60)
  - "Sailing Home", words and music by Walter G. Samuels, Leonard Whitcup, and Teddy Powerll, Words and Music Inc., pages 3-5, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "Santa Claus Is Comin' To Town", words by Haven Gillespie, music by J. Fred Coots, Fox Trot, 4 pages, 1934 (Box 60)
  - "Sandman", annotations, 1953 (Box 60)
  - "Shadows In The Night", words and music by Will Lorin, 5 pages, 1940 (Box 60)
  - "Silvery Moon and Golden Sands", by Harry Pease, Billy Haid and Larry Stock, Mills Music Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "Sing A Song of Sunbeams", lyrics by Johnny Burke, music by James V. Monaco, Santly Joy Select Inc., 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "Sing For Your Supper", words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, Chappell andCo., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "Sing, My Heart", words by Ted Koehler, music by Harold Arlen, Crawford Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Skylark", lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Hoagy Carmichael, Edwin H. Morris and Company, Inc., New York, 3 pages, 1942 (Box 60)
  - "Sleepy Lagoon", words by Jack Lawrence, music by Eric Coates, Chappell and Co., Ltd., pages 3-5, 1930 (Box 60)
  - "Softly Thru The Summer Night", 6 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "So Help Me", words by Eddie De Lange, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, 5 pages, 1 part, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "Some Enchanted Evening", words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, Williamson Music Inc., New York, pages 3-7, 1949 (Box 60)
  - "Some Rainy Day", by Carmon Lomabardo and John Jarob Loeb, Olman Music Corporation, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Something Wonderful", words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 4 pages, 1951 (Box 60)
  - "Somewhere In Heaven", words and music by Margaret Shellford, U.S. Music Inc., New York, 2 pages; "I Just Came Back For My Heart", Kathleen Cotter Fross and Elmo Russ, U.S. Music Inc., New York, 2 pages, 1949, 1950 (Box 60)
  - "Sonnet", Shakespeare, Joseph Enos, 4 pages, 1952 (Box 60)
  - "South American Way", lyrics by Al Dubin, music by Jimmy McHugh, Harms, Inc., New York, 1 part, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Speak Low", Ogden Nash, music by Kurt Well, Chappell and Co., N.Y.C., 1 part, 1943 (Box 60)
  - "Sweet Varsity Sue", by Charles Tobias, Al Lewis, Murray Mencher, 4 pages, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "Tell It To A Star", words and music by Shirley Botwin, 3 pages, 1942 (Box 60)
  - "Tell Me and I'll Tell A Million", words by Jack Finneran, music by Rovert Wyatt and George Sumner, 2 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Thank Heaven For Little Girls", words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, Chappell and Co., Inc., 5 pages, 1957 (Box 60)
  - "Thank You For The Lovely Summer", by Bart Howard, 3 pages, 1952 (Box 60)
  - "That Cute Little Gown of Gray", words by Clinton G. Sabin, music by Lawrence A, Weber, 2 pages, 1950 (Box 60)
  - "That's Him", words by Odgen Nash, music by Kurt Weill, Chappell and Co., Inc., N.Y.C., 4 pages, 1943 (Box 60)
  - "That Sly Old Gentleman", lyrics by Johnny Burke and music by James V. Monaco, Frances Day, Paris, France, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "Then Came The Rain", words by Charlie Tobias, music by Oscar Levant, 5 pages, 1 part, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "There Are Rivers To Cross, (Before We Meet Again)", words by Stanley Adams, music by Ray Henderson, 5 pages, 1942 (Box 60)
  - "There I Go", lyrics by Hy Zaret and music by Irving Weiser, 4 pages, 1940 (Box 60)
  - "They Say", lyrics by Edward Heyman, music by Paul Mann, and Stephan Weiss, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "This Can't Be Love", words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "This Is It", words by Dorothy Fields, music by Arthur Schwartz, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "This Is New", words by Ira Gershwin, music by Kurt Weill, 5 pages, 1941 (Box 60)
  - "This Is Madness (To Love Like This)", lyrics by Eddie De Lange, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "This Is My Night To Dream", from "Doctor Rhythm", lyrics by John Burke, music by James V. Monaco, Select Music Publications, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "This Is No Dream", words and music by Benny Davis, Tommy Dorsey and Ted Shapiro, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 60)
  - "This Time It's Real", words and music by Walter Shivers, Buddy Bernier and Bob Emmerich, 5 pages, 1938 (Box 60)
  - "This Year's Kisses", words and music by Irving Berlin, 4 pages, 1937 (Box 60)
  - "We Kiss In A Shadow", words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 5 pages, 1951 (Box 60)
  - "A Wonderful Guy", words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 7 pages, 1949 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, no title, 3 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, no title, 1 page (page 7), undated (Box 60)
  - Miscellanous, "No. 14 Couplets", 8 pages (page 126-134), undated (Box 60)
  - Music Scores, Holographic, Handwritten, 1929-1941 and undateds:
  - "A Call On Mr. President", Frida Sarsen-Bucky, 3 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Fling Wide The Gates", Harry Rowe Shelley, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Hear The Wind Whispering", Frida Sarsen-Bucky, 3 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "If I Were Queen, I'd Give My Horse A Holiday", Frida Sarsen-Bucky, 2 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Jack Frost", Frida Sarsen-Bucky, 3 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Lord, Do Thou Guide Me", music by A.W. Binder, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Moonlight Everywhere", Frida Sarsen-Bucky, 2 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "My Mother's Eyes", R. Huntington Woodman, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "121st Psalm", Karol Rathaus, G. Schirmer, Royal Brand, 7 pages, 10/28/1941 (Box 60)
  - "Out Of The East", lyrics and music by Harry Noble, 2 pages, 12/11/1929 (Box 60)
  - "Out Of The East", lyrics and music by Harry Noble, 2 pages, 12/11/1929 (Box 60)
  - "Praise The Lord, O My Soul", Anna Eliz. Gaeng, 2 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Showboat Medley", Carl Fischer, Inc., New York, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Stephen, Thy Demeanor Vary", (Undreadable) Broan, 5 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Sweet Music", Karol Rathaus, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "They That Sow In Tears", James H. Rodgers, 3 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Tour De Trois", 27 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "Three Up-To-Date Love Songs", words and music by Jessie Alexander, 9 pages, 1946 (Box 60)
  - "Throughout The Metidja To Abd El-Kadr", Robert Browning, 9 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "To A Wood Dove", poem by Theodore Dreiser, music by Lillian Rosedale Goodman, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - "To-day If You Will Hear His Voice", J.H. Roger, 1 page, undated (Box 60)
  - "The Voice In The Wilderness", John Prindle Scott, 4 pages, undated (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, no title, 1 page, undated (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, 29 pages of lesson from the Julliard School of Music, 1934 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous, no title, 1 page, undated (Box 60)
- Newspapers:
  - NEWSDAY, Vol. 24, No. 70, partial, 11/22/1963 (Box 51)
  - NEWSDAY, partial, 11/23/1963 (Box 51)
  - NEWSDAY, Vol. 24, No. 72, partial, 11/25/1963 (Box 51)
  - NEWSDAY, Vol. 24, No. 73, partial, 11/26/1963 (Box 51)
  - NEWSDAY, Vol. 29, No. 271, 07/21/1969 (Box 51)
  - New York Post, Vol. 163, No. 6, 11/22/1963 (Box 51)
  - New York Post, partial, 11/24/1963 (Box 51)
  - New York Post, partial, 11/25/1963 (Box 51)
  - New York Post, partial, 07/21/1969 (Box 51)
  - New York Times, Vol. CXIII, No. 38,655, 11/24/1963 (Box 51)
  - New York Times, Vol. CXVIII, No. 40,721, 07/21/1969 (Box 51)
  - VARIETY, Vol. 201, No. 6, 01/04/1956 (Box 51)
- Newspaper Clippings:
  - The Atlanta JOURNAL AND CONSTITUTION: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Birmingham NEWS: 5 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - The Boston DAILY GLOBE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Boston EVENING GLOBE: 2 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - The Boston GLOBE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Boston HERALD: 5 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston HYDE PARK TRIBUNE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston JAMAICA PLAIN CITIZEN: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston JEWISH ADVOCATE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston RECORD AMERICAN: 43 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston SUNDAY ADVERTISER: 14 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston SUNDAY GLOBE: 3 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Boston SUNDAY HERALD: 7 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago's AMERICAN: 7 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago DAILY NEWS: 6 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago DAILY TRIBUNE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago HERALD-AMERICAN, 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago SUN-TIMES, 5 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago TRIBUNE: 6 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Chicago TRIBUNE MAGAZINE: 5 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - THE CHRISTIAN SCIENCE MONITOR: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Cleveland PLAIN DEALER: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - THE CONCORD DAILY MONITOR AND N.H. PATRIOT: 2 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - THE DAILY JOURNAL: 2 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - DAILY NEWS: 9 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - The Denver POST: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Des Moines SUNDAY REGISTER and Bozeman DAILY CHRONICLE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Detroit NEWS: 2 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - Duluth NEWS TRIBUNE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - EVENING EXPRESS: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - EVENING INDEPENDENT: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - THE EVENING STAR: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Framingham NEWS: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - GIRL SCOUT COURIER: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - GLOBE-DEMOCRAT, SUNDAY: 2 pieces, undated (Box 61)
  - THE HARTFORD COURANT: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Houston Post: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Indianapolis TIMES: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - INTERNATIONAL HERALD TRIBUNE: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The JAMAICA STANDARD: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - THE JEWISH WEEK: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Laredo TIMES: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Lond Island Press: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - THE LONGVIEW DAILY NEWS: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - LOOK: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - Los Angeles TIMES: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Miami HERALD: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Miami NEWS: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - The Minneapolis STAR: 1 piece, undated (Box 61)
  - New Haven EVENING REGISTER: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - New Orleans STATE-ITEM: 8 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - Newport DAILY NEWS: 3 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - NEWSDAY: 3 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - NEWS OF THE SCHOOLS: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - New York HERALD TRIBUNE: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - New York JOURNAL-AMERICAN: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - The New York MIRROR: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - New York POST: 3 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - New York TIMES: 4 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - New York WORLD-TELEGRAM: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - Pittsburgh POST-GAZETTE: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - The Pittsburgh PRESS: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - THE POST-STANDARD: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - Providence JOURNAL: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - ROCKY MOUNTAIN NEWS: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - St. Louis GLOBE-DEMOCRAT: 10 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - St. Paul PIONEER PRESS: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - St. Petersburg INDEPENDENT: 3 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - St. Petersburg TIMES: 4 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - Echenectady GAZETTE: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - SENTINEL: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - SPARTANBURG HERALD: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - SUNDAY NEWS: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - SUNDAY, New York NEWS: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - THE SUNDAY REGISTER: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - TIMES-PICAYUNE: 5 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - TIMES-UNION: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - The Toole BULLETIN: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - VARIETY: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - The Washington DAILY NEWS: 1 piece, undated (Box 62)
  - WORLD JOURNAL TRIBUNE: 2 pieces, undated (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous: 22 pieces, undated (Box 62)
- Periodical: THE SATURDAY EVENING POST, Vol. 225, No. 19, 11/08/1952 (Box 62)
- Phonograph Records:
  - Ann Crowley, "Lili" and "I Get So Lonely", 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Carousel-Waltz", Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, Rodgers, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "The Continental", and "June Is Bustin' Out All Over", The Music of Morton Gould, 78 rpm, 05/31/1945 (Box 63)
  - "Engfuenrung Aus Dem Serail", Martem Aller Arten, Lilli Lehmann, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Great Day", Morton Gould and his Orchestra, CBS, Major Bowea "Shower of Stars", and "Dichture Talle" Tannhauser, Morton Gould and his Orchestra, CBS, "Shower of Stars", 78 rpm, 04/26/1945 (Box 63)
  - "Long Ago and Far Away" and "St. Louis Blues", Morton Gould, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Mignon: Overture", Arturo Toscanin and the NBC Symphony Orchestra, Abroise Thomas, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Milk and Honey", The Original Cast Recording, Robert Weede, Mimi Benzell and Molly Picon, 6 copies, 33 1/3 rpm, 1961 (Box 63)
  - "Mimi Benzell", microgroove, 33 1/3 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Mimi Benzell and Robert Merill", 78 rpm, 08/11/1959 (Box 63)
  - Morton Gould, "Fortune Teller's Scenario", 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - Morton Gould, "Tiger Rag" and "Hallelujiah", 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Old Time Medley", "Liza", 78 rpm, 07/19/1945 (Box 63)
  - "Personalities In Print", Leo Cherne, William Hillman, Mimi, Col. Stanley Schrotel and Clifton R. Read, 33 1/3 rpm, 09/09/1957 (Box 63)
  - "Play Your Hunch", 33 1/3 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "Smoke Gets In Your Eyes", Norman Cordon Show, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - "You Go To My Head", and "The Very Though of You", "I'll Be Seeing You", 78 pages, undated (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Part 1: 1. Opening - Cresta Blanca, 2. Closing - Cresta Blanca, 3. Opening - Teaberry; Part 2: 1. Middle - Teaberry, 2. Opening - Highway 50, 3. Closing - Highway 50, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Unidentified, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
  - Miscellaneous, Unidentified, 78 rpm, undated (Box 63)
- Photographs, Oversized: 16 x 20, Portrait of Mimi Benzell, matted, undated (Box Oversize)
- Photographs:
  - 11 x 14, Cast from movie, "Dark of the Sun", Yvette Mimeux, Jimmy Brown, Rod Taylor, and 2 unidentified actos, interviews, undated (Box 64)
  - 10 3/4 x 13 3/4, Candid shots of Mimi Benzell, 1964 (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Candid shots of Mimi Benzell and unidentified people, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, "Beautiful Lee Remick (n), chats with WNBC Radio's Mimi Benzell at the star-studded premiere of Columbia Pictures, LORD JIM, at the Loew's State Theatre, Benefit of Damon Runyon Cancer Fund, 1 copy, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Walter Gould, Jennifer Gould and Jonathan Gould, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Walter Gould, Jonathan Gould, inside a cover, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Peter O'Toole, Mimi Benzell and unidentified woman, radio interview, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Hugh O'Brien, and Chris Noel, radio interview, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Margo and Marek. Harst Burchalt, radio interview, undated (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Marty Allen and unidentified men and women, 12/1966 (Box 64)
  - 8 x 10, Mimi Benzell, Celeste Holm and unidentified man and woman, 05/1961 (Box 64)